NYSUT New York Special Task Force on Equity and Excellence in Education Files 6174/007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- NYSUT Commission on Equitable Public School Funding 1/6/82, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Letter from Hobart to members of the NYSUT Commission on Equitable Public School Funding re special meeting on January 6, 1982, to discuss Levittown decision, work of Rubin Task Force (NYS Special Task Force on Equity and Excellence in Education), December 2, 1981